http://www.moviemistakes.com/privacy

Add somethingLog in / sign upCinema/rental chartsCommon mistakesMost popular moviesMovie Mistakes BlogDiscord serverPlay F**k, Marry, KillPatreon pageMistakes/trivia booksMovie Mistakes subredditMovie trivia subreddit NotificationsTo know when people like your submissions, answer your questions, reply to you, etc., please create a free account and log in. Premium membership is also available for just $12 a year, which removes all adverts, prioritises your submissions, and more.Other areas Most popular pagesHome Alone 2: Lost in New York mistakesFamily Guy mistakesHome Alone 2: Lost in New York questions33 biggest mistakes in Toy Story moviesBeowulf endingShaun of the Dead triviaSuper Troopers quotesPauly Shore movies & TV showsTransformers: Revenge of the Fallen mistake pictureThe Truman Show plot Mistakes by genreAction moviesAnimation moviesBond moviesComedy moviesDisney moviesFantasy moviesHistory moviesHorror moviesMarvel moviesRomance moviesSci-fi moviesThriller moviesWar moviesWestern movies MoviesMost mistakes of 2020Best movie quotesMistakes in current releasesMovie quotesMovie triviaOscar nomineesMost mistake-prone directorsPlot summaries and movie spoilersRandom movie TVBest TV mistakesMost TV mistakesBest TV picturesMost popular TV showsBest TV quotesTV triviaBest TV mistakes of 2020Random TV show Blog postsThe biggest mistakes of 2020The 20 biggest Friends mistake picturesThe biggest mistakes in the Harry Potter moviesThe 20 biggest mistakes in The Wizard of Oz25 mistakes you never noticed in great moviesThe 20 biggest mistakes in Jurassic Park50 mistakes in The SimpsonsBiggest Bond movie mistakes40 biggest mistakes in The Big Bang Theory33 biggest mistakes in Toy Story moviesThe Biggest Movie Mistakes of the Decade18 bits of trivia for Toy Story moviesBiggest Christmas movie mistakesThe biggest mistakes in the X-Men moviesStan Lee's best cameos Other areasBrowse all titlesTrivia updatesGeneral questionsDVD Easter eggsRandom mistake pictureRandom bookRandom game Site infoMembershipAbout the siteTop membersMailing listFAQLinksSite mapContactPrivacy policy
Best mistakes Best pictures New this month Best comedy quotes Most mistakes Questions Movie quote quiz IMDb top 250 Best of 2020 Privacy policymoviemistakes.com keeps no personal information on record that is not knowingly provided. Cookies are used to save some user settings - by using this website you agree to let cookies be placed on your device.E-mail addresses given by non-members when adding entries to the site are used solely for the purpose of contacting people about any issues relating to their submission, and are not required from any visitor. Once a submission is entered onto the site, the contributor's e-mail address is deleted. Names and email addresses provided by registered members are used for the same reason, and are retained solely for the purpose of notifications and crediting submissions. Personal information is not passed to any third party. Any registered member who does not wish to be credited with their username can request that via the contact form or remove their username entirely.We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.aspThird party vendors and ad networks, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website.Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. For more information on how Google uses cookies, please visit https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites.Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings.Users may opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.Google Analytics is used for traffic analysis, however IP addresses are anonymised and no personally identifiable information is collected.By adding content to moviemistakes.com, you grant moviemistakes.com the right to reuse and republish it in any form. All content may be edited or discarded at moviemistakes.com's discretion.This product includes GeoLite data created by MaxMind, available from http://www.maxmind.com.All images on the site are © copyright their respective owners. If anyone has any questions or concerns about use of copyrighted material on moviemistakes.com, please e-mail me. XJoin the mailing listSeparate from membership, this is to get updates about mistakes in recent releases. Addresses are not passed on to any third party, and are used solely for direct communication from this site. You can unsubscribe at any time.
Name
Email
Join the mailing list Check out the mistake & trivia books, on Kindle and in paperback.
Add somethingLog in / sign upMistake & trivia booksMost popular pagesBest movie mistakesBest mistake picturesBest comedy movie quotesMovies with the most mistakesNew this monthHome Alone 2: Lost in New York mistakesFamily Guy mistakesHome Alone 2: Lost in New York questions33 biggest mistakes in Toy Story moviesBeowulf endingShaun of the Dead triviaSuper Troopers quotesPauly Shore movies & TV showsTransformers: Revenge of the Fallen mistake pictureThe Truman Show plotLatest blog postsThe biggest mistakes of 2020The 20 biggest Friends mistake picturesThe biggest mistakes in the Harry Potter moviesThe 20 biggest mistakes in The Wizard of Oz25 mistakes you never noticed in great moviesThe 20 biggest mistakes in Jurassic Park50 mistakes in The SimpsonsBiggest Bond movie mistakes40 biggest mistakes in The Big Bang Theory33 biggest mistakes in Toy Story movies
